Interfaith Worker Justice Records 6414
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Interfaith Worker Justice Records
1968-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Interfaith Worker Justice
6414
33 cubic feet
33 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Correspondence, appeals, budgets, committee information, and meeting minutes are some of the records included in this collection.
9431339
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, May 26, 2017
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, May 26, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6414 AV: Interfaith Worker Justice Audio-Visual Materials 6414 (d): Interfaith Worker Justice Records Digital 6414 G: Interfaith Worker Justice Posters 6414 MB: Interfaith Worker Justice Memorabilia
Interfaith Workers Justice (Organization); Bobo, Kimberley A.
9431339
- Online Solicitation, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Labor Day Appeal, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Blank Contribution Cards
- Lutheran Resources Mailing, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Year End 2004 Appeal (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Annual Report Mailing, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Living Wages for All
- Direct Mail Appeal, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Mailing Duplicates
- June 2004 Appeal (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fundraising Plan, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Online Appeal, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Year End Appeal, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  NICWJ Information
- Welcome Letter, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Young Catholic Workers, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  USPS Receipt; Letter Template; List of names
- Presbyterian Appeal, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Presbyterian List; Information Packet
- Union Lybunt, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Letter Template
- Maureen Sullivan - CST 2003 Summer Intern Solicitation (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Presbyterian Fundraising Project, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Information Packet
- August Online Solicitation, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- July Online Solicitation, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- April Solicitation to Non-Givers, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- March Solicitation, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Invoice
- January Non-giver, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Support the work information
- Year-End Appeals, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Jewish Donor Appeal, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Testimonials
- Spring Appeal, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Letter
- Spring Direct Appeal, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Marx - Board Appeal, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Fall 2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Winter2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- March CST Appeal, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Mailing Template
- May/June Appeal, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Winter Appeal Letter, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- December CTA Mailing, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Workers' Memorial Day Appeal, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- May/June Direct Appeal, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Year End Appeal, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fall Mailing (2,000 Yellow sheets), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- David Wilhelm Letter, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Dewitt's Direct Mail Letter, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Spring Board Appeal, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Direct Mail Letter, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Methodist Global Consultation, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Fall Direct Mail Planning, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Chicago Direct Mail, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Fundraising Letter - IL AFLCIO, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Egan Bishops Letter, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- December Year End Appeal, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- June Fundraising Appeal, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Equal Justice Center (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Worker Justice Fund (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Worker Justice Fund (Box 1, Folder 50)
- WJ Fund Budget, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Money Pool (Box 1, Folder 52)
- WJ Fund Grants Committee (Box 1, Folder 53)
- East Bay Interfaith Committee (Box 1, Folder 54)
- New Orleans Interfaith (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Georgia Poultry Justice Alliance, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Washington Association of Churches, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- WJF Recommendation Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Arkansas Interfaith Committee (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Cleveland JWJ, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Syracuse, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Cincinnati, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- New Haven, CT, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Eugene - Springfield Solidarity Network, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Honolulu, HI, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- KY JWJ, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Massachusetts Interfaith, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Montana, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- San Diego, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Iowa Faith Labor, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Las Vegas, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  The Nevada Book of Shame
- Pueblo, CO, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Rochester, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- South Florida, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Southern Arizona Alliance for Economic Justice, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- St. Joseph Valley Project, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Oregon Farmworker Ministry, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Staten Island, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- IA/NE, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- San Jose, CA, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Grant Committee, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Washington State, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Progressive MD Educational Fund, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Missouri Citizen Education Fund, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Buffalo, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Calumet Hammond, IN, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Long Island, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Oregon - WFJ, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Oregon - Eugene, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- St. Joseph Valley, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Worker Justice Grant Committee (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Tucson. Southern Arizona, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Philadelphia, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Madison, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Reno, Nevada, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Syracuse/ Central New York, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Orlando, FL, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Cincinnati, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Cleveland, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Arkansas, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- January WJ Fund, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Kentucky, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Massachusetts Interfaith, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Memphis, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Vermont, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Fairfield County, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Oakland, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Fall Requests, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Detroit Interfaith, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Metro Atlanta, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Hartford (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Long Island, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Monterey, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Southern Tier, NY, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Map
- Good Jobs Evaluation, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Waterbury Interfaith Committee (Box 2, Folder 40)
  Guidebook
- Religious Leaders Concerned, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Washington Association of Churches, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Detroit, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Twin Cities, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Madison, South Central Wisconsin, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Iowa, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- South Florida, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Rochester, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  Campaign to Stop Child Labor and Poster Exhibit
- San Diego, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Organization Department (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Seminary Summer Quotes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Summer Student Internships, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  Folder
- Summer Interns, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  Agenda
- Habakkuk (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Religious Perspectives on Work (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Workers' Letters (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Strategic Plan, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Strategic Plan, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Strategic Plan, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Taproot Foundation (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Stored Value Project, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Fundraising Reports, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Training Program (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Moral Economy (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Building DC Office (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Employee Free Choice Act, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride (Box 2, Folder 67)
- CINTAS Campaign (Box 2, Folder 68)
  Chicago Interfaith Committee on Worker Issues
- Public Worker Support (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Affiliation Core Standards (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Backwages.org (Box 2, Folder 71)
- CMBDT (Box 2, Folder 72)
- AFL-CIO Report, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- SS Agenda, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Emergency Contact, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Expenses, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- SS Articles, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Summer Interns Evaluations, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Expenses, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Reflections, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Seminary Summer, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- SS Evaluations, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- SS Mentors Fielded (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Debrief (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Travel (Box 3, Folder 13)
- SS Orientation Handouts (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Site Applications (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Seminary Summer Expenses, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Freedom Rides (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Minimum Wage (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Murray Coal (Box 3, Folder 19)
- PBGC (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Peabody Coal (Box 3, Folder 21)
- SEIU - Chicago MC (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Sky Chefs (Box 3, Folder 23)
- SSA No Match (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Teamsters (Box 3, Folder 25)
- UFCW (Box 3, Folder 26)
- UFE Eco Education Project (Box 3, Folder 27)
- USF Dugan (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Voter Registration (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Wal-Mart Watch (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Affiliate Agreement (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Blue Mountain June, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Photos
- Chicago Islam Labor Conference, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- October Gathering, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- May Conference, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- National Conference, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- National IWJ Conference, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- IWJ Summer/ Seminary Summer Work plan, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- IWJ/CST Summer, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Board Source Materials (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Grassroots Fundraising Journal (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Gulf Coast Commission on Reconstruction Equity (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Training - Organization Department on Msg/Speaking (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Training - Organization Department - Meeting Facilitation (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Training Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Training - Religion - Labor Weeklong September, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Religion - Labor Organizing Training, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Training - Local Groups - Board (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Training - Union on Interfaith (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Student Training - February, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Workers Center Training - March, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Worker Center Highlander (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Curriculum (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Workers Memorial Day, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Worker Justice Fund, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- CHD Worker Justice Fund Report (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Worker Justice Report (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Faithful Citizenship Summer (Box 3, Folder 58)
- IWJ Training Programs (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Fundraising Pre-Conference (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Local Chapter Information (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Student Training - February, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Media (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fundraising (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Fundraising and the Board (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Reaching Out to Religious Community (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Strengthening Religious Outreach (Box 4, Folder 9)
- September 17-21, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Workers' Center Training - March, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- A Dialogue Between the Religious and Labor Community on Social and Ethical Concerns in a Changing Society - January 25-27, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- The Religion and Labor Conference: Its Preparation and Creation, 1978 to 1982 - May, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Sharing the Harvest - June, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Forging Partnerships for a new Millennium - October, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Accomplishments, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Seminary Summer Orientation - June, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Labor Management Project Advising Committee - October, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ohio Valley Training for Faith and Worker Justice - January, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Economic Justice Learning Track: NAEIS Conference - July, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Economic Justice Learning Track: NAEIS Conference - July [copy], 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Planted by the water - A Tribute to Monsignor Higgins - September, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- The Prophetic Work: Religion and Labor Uniting for Worker Justice - May, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- The Prophetic Work: Religion and Labor Uniting for Worker Justice - May [copy 2], 2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Plenary I: Sunday Evening, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Board Orientation Manual (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Taking on "Big Chicken": The Delmarva Poultry Justice Alliance - Summer, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Summer Internship Orientation Week - June 13-18, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Labor in the Pulpits: Speaking Out for Worker Justice, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- 2005 National Conference - May 22-24 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- 2005 Summer Internship - June 16-24 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Religion-Labor Organizing Training - September 19-21, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- 2006 Summer Internship - June 8-16 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Peabody Energy: Rights Denied and Promises Broken - July 16-17, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Building a Local Chapter - July, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Religion-Labor Organizer Training - September 9-13, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Come Walk With Us - June 16-19, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- The Power of Interfaith, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Summer Internships Orientation Week - June 8-13, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Leadership Summit - June 13-15, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Organizing for Worker Justice Training - November 1-5, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Organizing for Worker Justice Training - November 1-5 (copy 2), 2009 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Ascension Health: A Fall from Grace - July 15, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Board of Director, Advisors, Staff Address Book, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Forging the Flame of Justice - June 19-21, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Forging the Flame of Justice - June 19-21 (copy 2), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Organizing for Worker Justice Training - October 14-19, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Wage Theft: Crime and Justice, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Faith Work Justice (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Conference, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- IWJ Fundraising Grant Materials (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Staff Retreat, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Staff Retreat, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Staff Retreat, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Staff Retreat, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Staff Retreat, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Staff Retreat, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Social Forum/Retreat, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Staff Retreat, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Staff Retreat, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Pittston Strike, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Pittston Church Meeting - March 8-9, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Pittston Religious Leaders' Statements (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Newlywed Foods, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- RA Briggs, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Caterpillar, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- O'Hare Workers, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Striker Replacement Bill, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Fieldcrest Cannon, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Strawberry Workers, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Guess, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Crown Petroleum, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Kroger-West VA, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Smith Barney, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- UPS, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Copperhill, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Melrose - Hilton Head, SC, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- M. Fine Sons (Louisville, KY), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Townsend, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Wheeling/Pittsburg Strike, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Copperhill, NC, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Notes (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Bridgestone/Firestone, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- K-Mart, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- City Hospital of Akron, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Bridgestone Firestone, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Detroit Newspaper Strike, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- AgriGlobal Egg Farm - LaRue, Ohio, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Case Farms, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Religious Employers (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Grace Students - U of IL, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Kenwood Healthcare Center, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Delta Flight Attendants, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Minimum Wage Bill, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- GE Contract, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Kaiser Aluminum, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Overnight Transport, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Prestonburg, KY, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Goya Foods, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Titan, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Christmas Tree Workers, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Nissan, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Offshore Mariners United, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Ergo Standard, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Overtime, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Voter Registration, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Boeing, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Grocery Strike, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- USF Dugan, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- America West Airlines, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Advocate Healthcare, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Boeing in Wichita, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Cintas, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Immigrant Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Pre-Apprenticeship Materials (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Transition Documents (Box 5, Folder 65)
- WCN Coordinator Resumes (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Workers stories for Congressional Hearing (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Summit, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Workers Centers (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Chicago Interfaith Workers Rights Center (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Workers Defense Project - Austin (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Central Carolina Workers Center Beloved Community Center, NC (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Western NC Workers Center (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Voces de la Frontera Workers Center - Milwaukee (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Newspaper
- Workers Interfaith Network (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Young Workers United (Box 6, Folder 8)
- ROC NY (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Immigrant Workers Center Study (Box 6, Folder 10)
- New Centers (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Travel/Reg. Forms Summit, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Nola (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Madison Workers Rights Center (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Interfaith Workers Justice Center - Arkansas (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Houston Interfaith Worker Justice Center (Box 6, Folder 16)
  First Annual Report 2006-2007
- Convening Notes - September, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Workers Center Network (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Wage Theft (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Convening - September, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Network Gatherings (past) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- CLC Partnerships (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Archdiocese of Chicago - Construction Contracts (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Catholic Charities - Just Faith Parish Social Min (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Catholic-Labor Network (Box 6, Folder 26)
- The Catholic Social Ministry Gathering - February 22-25, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Catholic Social Ministry, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Community Service Liaison Program (Box 6, Folder 29)
- EPI/EARN (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Annual Conference - October 17-19, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Jobs with Justice (Box 6, Folder 32)
- National Campaign Jobs Income Support (Box 6, Folder 33)
- The Roundtable Annual Symposium - February 21-22, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Roundtable (Archdio Peace) Justice (Box 6, Folder 35)
- WILG (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Workers Injury Law Advocacy Group
- America West (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Childcare, SEIU (Box 6, Folder 38)
- ComCast (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Co-op Mine - Utah (Box 6, Folder 40)
- EFCA Human Rights - December 10, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Grocery Strike/ So. CA (Box 6, Folder 42)
- HERE - 2002 Hotel Contract Campaign, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Patriot Coal/ Peabody Coal (Box 6, Folder 44)
  Fighting for Fairness Folder
- George Higgins (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Jack Egan (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Back wages (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Katrina/ Gulf Rebuilding (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Ethical Business Campaign (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Labor-Management Project (Box 6, Folder 50)
- End-year Progress Report, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Update - October 1, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Funder Updates - February, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Progress Report - October, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Year-End Report, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Hyatt Hotel Campaign, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Republic Airlines, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Cintas, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Northwest Mechanics Strike, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  August 2005
- Ice "Ruse", 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Allied-Barton, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Employee Free Choice Act, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Walmart, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Cintas, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Cintas Delegation Materials, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Cintas Campaign, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Cintas OSHA Violations Rochester, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Cintas OSHA Violations- Bedford Park Schaumburg, IL, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Cintas OSHA Violations- Branford, CT, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cintas OSHA Violations- San Leandro, CA, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Cintas Partner Reference Guide, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  personnel policy
- Cintas healthcare, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cintas Drivers Suit, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cintas Research, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Cintas OSHA-general, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Cintas Living Wage Issues, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Cintas OSHA Violations- Pico Rivera, CA, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Cintas Partners' Plan, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Retirement
- Cintas-shop towels, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Cintas- environmental concerns, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Cintas Briefing Book, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- CIWTAS, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Cintas Current, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Cintas Anti-Union Activity, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Cintas Report, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Cintas Fact Sheets, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Back-up Documents Seeking Fresh Linens, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Cintas Fact Finding, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Cintas, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Cintas- General Documents, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Cintas- End of 104, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Cintas Complaints, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Seminary Summer, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Seminary Summer plus CST, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Seminary Summer, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Alan Abrams, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Tammy Banjany, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Mindy Bell, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Ann Bonner, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- JoAnn Campbell-Sudduth, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Mary-Craig Caruthers, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Mary Climer, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Bob Crystal, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Jen Flam, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Laura Folkwein, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Mark Goodman, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Alice Harper Jones, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Gerald Jones, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Margaret Keig, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Nicole Lake, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Teran Loeppke, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Carol Masson, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Joseph Mokos, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- John Kennedy Onoba, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Ryan O'Rourke, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Kliel Rose, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Stephanie French, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Mike Rothbaum, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Devorah Shubowitz, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Josh Steward, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Virginia Trabulsi, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Trina Ward, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Salying Wong, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Adan Sandoval, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Joseph Boland, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Karen Landahl, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Mark Swanson, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Cristina Airaghi, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Billy Byrnes, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Duane Bartz, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Heather Chase, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Melissa James, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Karen Landahl (Box 8, Folder 44)
- David Lysy, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Sarah Meyrowitz, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Robyn McPherson, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Eugen Nagy, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Arnold Yesu Raj, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 49)